Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Who's afraid? Let it break
From shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown
The Psyche awakens, you're never...
be unexpected.
Cheers to the friends, the story gets stranger, it never ends
psyche's show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand the angels are dancing torchlight in
hand let's start the show
okay i'll be right here hello
uh you see it i just saw it flash
Hey, Jamie Rose. What's up? Hey, dust dog, right there.
That a great dinner. We're good? Okay. Okay. What's up, Jamie Rose? Let me see. I can probably try to bring, but we're just walking down the street.
Hi, I kidnapped psyche. I kidnapped them. Just so everyone knows
Hello
For the night
I'm just going wherever I'm told
We're just walking on Zika
this is a nice nice little dark street though it's like a there's no there's hardly any street lights
how are you guys doing let's see what's up jamie rose jamie rose i wish i got a yes i got you sorry
so i think i think jamie rose is saying what's up girl or unless i'm like i'm like blind hold on
It's hard on
Where is old girl, okay, I'm old girl
And I'm a girl
There we go, they can see me. There you go. Hi. You just put it for the lab. We're getting to it
We're getting to light soon. Oh, there's a lady. We're scared. I keep slowing him down
Not at all
like
I'm in some city, but here's the desktops of the chat. Okay, so let's see
Okay
So video no idea home. So video full screen. I need to fix my video. I think we need to put a full screen
Turn it sideways
Well, I mean
It's not changing on the stream yard. So I don't know guys. I'm a little bit too drunk to figure out
I think I had like, I had five drinks.
He has to walk it off.
Who said, did somebody send her to give me drunken and take me back to an undisclosed location?
Oh, I don't know.
Fortunately, it's a very safe neighborhood from what I can observe.
It is.
I don't think there's any trouble amidst from what I can observe.
It's beautiful.
I don't even, my door wasn't even locked.
I don't even lock my house.
I don't know, I do lock, everybody in chat,
I do lock my house, I do.
There's actually a vicious guard cat
so that will tear you apart to come in.
I walk way too fast.
Oh my God, I've been walking fast.
Hey, I'm not trying to like get her out of bed.
No, it's okay. It's my challenge for the night. I'm out of I'm out of breath ever. Okay. He's very athletic. He is tall
he is
ready to
Do a triathlon
Here I am
We did well, we had the best we had the best dinner
Make it up this hill, but I will make it you are very naturally athletic not to be
stereotypical
I might not make it.
I...
She keeps up...
Well, we just keep up with each other naturally.
I think we're like both...
We're in the same speed.
Yeah, it's Capricorns.
What is today?
What is the official day?
It's 9.20...
Hold on.
9.22.
Okay.
So number nine and nine is like German to know to two
Yeah
Powerful I pull four few times today like as a car
I mean, there's like there's like dualities, but then the dualities matching with other dualities. That's like all
It's like everything's balanced. Everything's balancing. We're on the square. We're officially on our squares
Well, you know
You know, I think even people we hate the most maybe they can be like somehow regime. I don't know. I
Don't want to like throw away any soul
You know, you don't waste a good soul. There might be good souls out there that like can now can be like cleaned off or something
in the name of all that is good.
May the balance of psyche and Alex create balance
to where there's no more meanness
from whoever's mean out there.
Oh yeah, summer's here, let's see.
Oh my gosh, thank you for, hold on, hold on.
Maybe not, hold on, let's see.
Oh yeah, I have my wrong thing on.
Okay.
I'm just too drunk, okay.
Okay, he says tell Alexandra to keep her hands off my man a little well, okay
No, Alexander. I will not do that. I've got him
Are you an alexander like evil twins? I like I don't know
Can you believe calling you alexander they do they go they do they call me alexander instead of alexandra
My name is alexandra
Drugs drugs drugs, but who's this Boston soul says got lost on the way to the glory hole
What does that mean? Oh me?
No, we are not vegan patriots. I've never been to one glory
I would like I would there's no there's no like whole carp in a toilet stall that would be attractive enough for me to
My mouth on no matter how big the penis was I was just being too disgusting. I mean
Yeah, I mean it's like I would never go there's no glory. It has to be like, you know
But who would have to be that in a glory or
The war hole doesn't exist. Not a glory holds and been made good enough for me. Yeah
Okay
I'm so sorry. I'm walking so fast
We are like actual like we are the goats of climbing though. It's like a whole block
I'm not the land of grass
No, I need a force I need to figure out how to turn my screen, but
I don't know it's it's so complicated when both stream yard and well, you'd have to go into the settings. Yeah
Too complicated
Well, it's pretty much put upside down it would look better than that would
Where do we go?
Okay, okay guys we're lost in the middle of my city. I don't know. I don't know the city
Maybe we should walk back. I only live here for ten years. We're gonna go back to the car
Yeah, okay, we're gonna walk back to the car. I think we got lost. Yeah on the way
We walked we streamed there. We are
We walked and we stream there might be another stream another time it might be soon it might be later
But we're streaming
This is IRL
What I don't know what's up with ip2 ip2. Hello. Can you just advertise for us ip2? I mean just like, okay, film me
I gotta do something that's I'm not supposed to. Yeah, I mean, I mean forget an ip2. You'd have to like
I don't know. I mean all they all they do is gay and like drunk stuff
I mean, you just get really drunken gay like me
I've got you. Okay. Well, wait, let's go in the light here over here.
People believe I think people think that I'm just pretending. No, well, maybe, maybe. Here we are. We're here. We're streaming. We are IRL 40 plus edition.
Yeah, what we're gonna do. I don't know but
You know you tell him
No, I don't know the area. Okay. Well, let's have to walk until we're at your car
Eventually we'll get to her car
I feel Jonathan Pendo is saying WTF
We're going to go back to the main track and what the intersection we're going to make a left. Okay. Then we'll make a right
Guys, did you see us turn down any streets or do we just?
Okay, we're in straight. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, so I I didn't see it
What did I have for dinner? You remember?
Um, well, you didn't eat that much. You had the fish tacos. I did have fish tacos
There were there were the best fish tacos I ever had
In my life I had a skirt steak skirt steak and mozzarella sticks. That's my staple. I always had the mozzarella stick
We had drinks. I had wine you had you had exotic drinks, right?
I had the oh, I had the og and I had what's called the og and then I had one called
The peach something it was like a it was something. Yeah, it's peachy. Yeah
There's and then tequila and if there was called ranch water
I don't know what's in that that was tequila and like club soda and like lime. It was really good
Okay, let's okay. Yeah, that way we can walk up the main. Okay
Look at this cool light
Oh Shania colors, too
Did that do it for us? That's weird. Oh, yeah
There it goes
I mean, I'm gonna dance on the pole for a second.
I might, I might, but I'm afraid that the guy will come out with a shotgun.
I mean, it looks like a little bit like, yeah, I'm not sure.
We're not looking for drama tonight.
Oh, there it is, the car. It's down there.
If we're looking for drama, all we gotta do is go on the panels.
Yeah.
Okay?
Whose panel is open did everyone hear us? I'm just on my phone and I hopefully I left it 100% but
Like you know how these phones drain like let me see. Yeah, I can't I can't even like read the screen or anything
I think we're over that way down that street. Okay
Watch out for the car
Okay, no, I didn't get
I was just
I'll try to pull you back, but it says no outlet on the street. What does that mean? They don't have electricity
No outlets. Oh
Yeah, I've been driven for a long time
Well, I make it I might know
Guys you have to you have to like stay tuned to our shows
I'm good, but they're not the sneaker chip
Minor from China
I'm a retrieving glasses. I should I wear the glass in the middle of the night. Yes
Really cool guys, that's right. I got vision I see anything coming. I'll tell you
Are we here? We're here. Oh, that's not my car. That's not your car. Okay. I can't show your car. So tell me when it's really
The restaurant is over here
Yeah, I don't know like two streets away from me. I all I know is the pier
And no, no, this is the right and I'm like blind right now. I know I'm blind
Here we are now there's some streetlight here I can see I can see in the light home
I just like I know I can see but the problem is I'm so drunk the words are all going all over the screen
Well, it says lowrider 65
Discord, I mean hey Alex. I see Alexander McQueen. I like and see is like some names
See Alexander and some pictures. I can't read words now. I'm sorry guys
Guys guys, this is a real IRL and if everybody doesn't go to ip2.info whatever this ip2.net work
Yeah, now you have to like we have to put me on there. Yeah and say
Like he's walking around in the middle of his neighborhood in the middle of the night
It's more interesting whatever that Victoria bitch is doing. So, uh, you know vote for him
Victoria, I'm sorry. I don't know you. I don't know you seem like a very nice person
I mean, it was kind of funny when she was yelling at her mom because her mom, like, she lives with her mom.
Yeah, well, she's disrespectful.
Yeah.
Okay, barrel screen?
Yeah, so this is barrel and prestige.
Look, there's a private party in Redondo Beach.
There's a private party in Redondo Beach.
Sketchers, a shoe party in Redondo Beach?
Where?
Why are you inviting us?
Because we're high.
We'll do thank you. Are you having a good night?
Good food. Oh, wow
Hey, thank you
Okay, we just got invited to a private party by some guy in a wheelchair and
Yeah, it's this way. Yeah
I was about to take us up the wrong street and I live on the street
I'm a little puppy right now.
I'm a little big hair, but I don't want to mad.
Big hair don't care, right?
Okay, we can go like behind the restaurant or it's right there, we can go through it.
Remember we had to go through it.
We can go through it again.
That's so fine.
Okay.
There you go.
Yeah.
They're not going to think anything is weird, they're going to be like, can you count the
money in the register a few more times?
This strange couple keeps coming, walking through.
Look, we're teens again.
We're walking at night, live streaming.
Yeah.
We don't know where we're going.
We're just walking how many people why is it? Why is there only? Oh my god? Oh, that's what he's everyone spread the word
What's happening? I mean, this is this is like major news reverse your aging. You got you higher
Okay
Okay, there's a construction
I don't know, I don't know where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know, where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know, where the nearest entrance is, I don't know, I don't know
Yeah, well, I know about it like going through the little corners and stuff like that. Yeah, that's always good
Okay. Oh, yeah
Okay, should I turn it off? Oh, yeah. Okay. Good night, guys
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream be the colonists learn words starting up a scene talking all that
trash then she flips rage queen mad at me girl please the show runs on caffeine
sights twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we
cut the feed no shame but the chats on fire can't tame this flame this ain't
your mama's podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up tight
boot flashing on cam chat losing their minds Michael getting gong
filter all facts yo all facts yo yo michael drops a line gong not tonight alex
tried to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways someone's got a
fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirt
slipping down low oops she says with a wink
The vibe